# Darjan Divkovic | Full Stack Web Developer / UI | UX Development

Email & GitHub: darjan.developer@gmail.com | GitHub

#### **Professional Profile**

' A multi-skilled Software Developer providing design-to-deployment services with a strong background in building Saas applications and other web related solutions.'

Mid level web developer with 3+ years of experience in the industry, engineering, building, maintaining, fixing and improving Saas web applications and other web related solutions for different clients, companies and customers. Experienced contractor that worked within Agile, Scrum and Kanban teams of varying sizes within multiple organizations bringing end to end solutions. Additionally has rich mentoring experience teaching trainees core programming skills. Provided and providing independent consultant services for multiple clients.

#### Core Skills

- JavaScript
- Vue.js
- Pvthon
- HTML5, Pug
- CSS3

- Sass, Less, SCSS
- Tailwind Css
- JQuerv
- React.js ( revisit )
- Cucumber

- Django (entry)
- Git, Github, GitLab
- Jira, Loom, ClickUp
- Figma
- Linux, Docker

### Career Summary

# Innoscripta AG - Munich, Bavaria - Remote Web Developer

2020 - 2021

- Worked within Agile teams of up to 5 people although the company had many teams at this point that did work with each other.
- Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues and solving client reports and maintaining code integrity and organization.
- Implemented design solutions for different marketing sites owned by company
- Maintained and updated marketing sites owned by company

# Pequity - San Francisco, CA - Remote

2021 - present

UI | UX Developer

- Implementing designs to pixel-perfect UI and third-party libraries and APIs.
- Worked within Agile, Kanban and Scrum teams with different member capacities ranging from 5 to 10 people and provided end-to-end solutions for clients.
- Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues and solving client reported issues.
- Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates.
- Worked on creating multiple different python scripts for automatically handling marketing initiative needs, handling bulk image files, mass scraping of companies, image manipulation etc.
- Collaborate with the rest of the engineering team to design and launch new features.
- Create and enhance features for the core web application platform using frontend technologies following company and industry best practices.
- Was a part of internal "Front End Guild" which worked on improving current front-end solutions
  according to new increasing market needs and improving the quality of the product overall as a
  part of side work.

### Independent Contractor Work

# **Client tracking software** - *private customer* - Remote *Independent Contractor*

2020

- Implemented client tracking solution for local non governmental organization to help manage and keep track of applicants for different types of services

# **Truck dispatch automation software** - *private customer* - Remote *Independent Contractor*

2023 - present

 Implemented and currently maintaining and extending automated software run by Python and Puppeteer that searches and scrapes important shipment offer data that is later uploaded to other desired sites via automated process.

#### Mentoring Experience

## BILD - IT - Tuzla, Bosnia and Herzegovina - On site

2019 - present

Trainee become mentor

- Obtained key knowledge in core programming principles learning Java as well as other soft skills
- Turned to mentor and continued to teach trainees in core professional and programming skills

# **Tuzla Summer Institute** - **Tuzla, Bosnia and Herzegovina** - On site **Facilitator**

2020

- Helped organize and prepare the event to teach different classes for people looking to get into programming
- Facilitated 5 day classes teaching version control principles through Git and GitHub

#### Education

BILD - IT - Programming

International Business Information Academy - Soon to be Bachelor of Computer Science and Informatics

Medical High School

## **Recommendation Letters**

Can be read on **LinkedIn**